[
    {
        "question": "بروك",
        "response": "بروك"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيفي",
        "response": "فيفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "روبين"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسوب",
        "response": "اوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "فرانكي",
        "response": "فرانكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيمبي",
        "response": "جيمبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاكسس",
        "response": "لاكسس"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماي",
        "response": "ماي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيغن",
        "response": "جيغن"
    },
    {
        "question": "هشيراما",
        "response": "هشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "روك لي",
        "response": "روك لي"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "روجر",
        "response": "روجر"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لولوش",
        "response": "لولوش"
    },
    {
        "question": "لايت",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "موب",
        "response": "موب"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريكا",
        "response": "ريكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينرا",
        "response": "شينرا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيفي",
        "response": "فيفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "واكاسا",
        "response": "واكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكاشي",
        "response": "اكاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوميكو",
        "response": "يوميكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثورز",
        "response": "ثورز"
    },
    {
        "question": "عبدول",
        "response": "عبدول"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكامي",
        "response": "اكامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوزيف",
        "response": "جوزيف"
    },
    {
        "question": "كينغ",
        "response": "كينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاك",
        "response": "لاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانيكي",
        "response": "كانيكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوراما",
        "response": "كوراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيسامي",
        "response": "كيسامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيساكي",
        "response": "كيساكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيسكي",
        "response": "كيسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوكو",
        "response": "غوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيراكو",
        "response": "هيراكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "روكيا",
        "response": "روكيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناو",
        "response": "كاناو"
    },
    {
        "question": "دازاي",
        "response": "دازاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيروتو",
        "response": "كيروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوكس",
        "response": "هوكس"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناغاتو",
        "response": "ناغاتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غاي",
        "response": "غاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مارلين",
        "response": "مارلين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميراجين",
        "response": "ميراجين"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايدو",
        "response": "كايدو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورابيكا",
        "response": "كورابيكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيجيتا",
        "response": "فيجيتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "راينر"
    },
    {
        "question": "سوكونا",
        "response": "سوكونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيزارو",
        "response": "كيزارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارثر",
        "response": "ارثر"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "روبين"
    },
    {
        "question": "تسونادي",
        "response": "تسونادي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زابزو",
        "response": "زابزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "زابوزا",
        "response": "زابوزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيستوريا",
        "response": "هيستوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناخت",
        "response": "ناخت"
    },
    {
        "question": "زاك",
        "response": "زاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلربي",
        "response": "كيلربي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسكانور",
        "response": "اسكانور"
    },
    {
        "question": "شويفيو",
        "response": "شويفيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوناثان",
        "response": "جوناثان"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريوم",
        "response": "ميريوم"
    },
    {
        "question": "اول مايت",
        "response": "اول مايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيدان",
        "response": "هيدان"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوهان",
        "response": "يوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "رين",
        "response": "رين"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورو",
        "response": "كورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "شانكس",
        "response": "شانكس"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاكاشي",
        "response": "كاكاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوتشي",
        "response": "لوتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوين",
        "response": "كوين"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوري",
        "response": "هوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياماتو",
        "response": "ياماتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياماموتو",
        "response": "ياماموتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كونان",
        "response": "كونان"
    },
    {
        "question": "نير",
        "response": "نير"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينوبو",
        "response": "شينوبو"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانيمي",
        "response": "سانيمي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوباناي",
        "response": "اوباناي"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيومي",
        "response": "غيومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناي",
        "response": "كاناي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيغاراكي",
        "response": "شيغاراكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوتو",
        "response": "شوتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "باكوغو",
        "response": "باكوغو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ياتو",
        "response": "ياتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "تويا",
        "response": "تويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتاما",
        "response": "اوتاما"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوتارو",
        "response": "جوتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديو",
        "response": "ديو"
    },
    {
        "question": "دراغون",
        "response": "دراغون"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "سابو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايس",
        "response": "ايس"
    },
    {
        "question": "غارب",
        "response": "غارب"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاك",
        "response": "هاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "بان",
        "response": "بان"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونا",
        "response": "يونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "ميليوداس"
    },
    {
        "question": "باجي",
        "response": "باجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كروكودايل",
        "response": "كروكودايل"
    },
    {
        "question": "دوفلامينغو",
        "response": "دوفلامينغو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميهوك",
        "response": "ميهوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "دابي",
        "response": "دابي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميغومي",
        "response": "ميغومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتادوري",
        "response": "ايتادوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوجي",
        "response": "يوجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سينكو",
        "response": "سينكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غون",
        "response": "غون"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلوا",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريوم",
        "response": "ميريوم"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيلفا",
        "response": "سيلفا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانزو",
        "response": "هانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوبيتو",
        "response": "اوبيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "توغا",
        "response": "توغا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابيتو",
        "response": "سابيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اريما",
        "response": "اريما"
    },
    {
        "question": "نورمان",
        "response": "نورمان"
    },
    {
        "question": "راي",
        "response": "راي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيكامارو",
        "response": "شيكامارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسوب",
        "response": "اوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "اندرا",
        "response": "اندرا"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونا",
        "response": "يونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوتو",
        "response": "شوتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناتسو",
        "response": "ناتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "لوسي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هابي",
        "response": "هابي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيريف",
        "response": "زيريف"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "راي",
        "response": "راي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اودين",
        "response": "اودين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايدوارد",
        "response": "ايدوارد"
    },
    {
        "question": "تيتش",
        "response": "تيتش"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللحية السوداء",
        "response": "اللحية السوداء"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللحية البيضاء",
        "response": "اللحية البيضاء"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيرو تو",
        "response": "زيرو تو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "اودين",
        "response": "اودين"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوين",
        "response": "كوين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاشي",
        "response": "ايتاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "response": "ساسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بياكويا",
        "response": "اكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سينتشي",
        "response": "سينتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاكيميتشي",
        "response": "تاكيميتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتسورا",
        "response": "كاتسورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جينتوكي",
        "response": "جينتوكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتاكوري",
        "response": "كاتاكوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكاينو",
        "response": "اكاينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيغ مام",
        "response": "بيغ مام"
    },
    {
        "question": "لينلين",
        "response": "لينلين"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكيجي",
        "response": "اوكيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماهيتو",
        "response": "ماهيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "موهيتو",
        "response": "موهيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديو",
        "response": "ديو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساي",
        "response": "ساي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوشينا",
        "response": "كوشينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساكورا",
        "response": "ساكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميهوك",
        "response": "ميهوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "تانجيرو",
        "response": "تانجيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوسكي",
        "response": "اينوسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كرولو",
        "response": "كرولو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "ميليوداس"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناو",
        "response": "كاناو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناي",
        "response": "كاناي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوجيتا",
        "response": "غوجيتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيك",
        "response": "زيك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميناتو",
        "response": "ميناتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نورمان",
        "response": "نورمان"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيريو",
        "response": "شيريو"
    },
    {
        "question": "جاك",
        "response": "جاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايتو كيد",
        "response": "كايتو كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبيراما",
        "response": "توبيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "لابون",
        "response": "لابون"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليون",
        "response": "ليون"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاواكي",
        "response": "كاواكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "شارلوك هولمز",
        "response": "شارلوك هولمز"
    },
    {
        "question": "شارلوك",
        "response": "شارلوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورو",
        "response": "كورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكي",
        "response": "اوكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تو",
        "response": "تو"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوسين",
        "response": "اوسين"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "كيوكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانكي",
        "response": "كانكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "response": "ساسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساكورا",
        "response": "ساكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسكي",
        "response": "ميتسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سارادا",
        "response": "سارادا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسوبيشي",
        "response": "ميتسوبيشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسوري",
        "response": "ميتسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوتا",
        "response": "يوتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "تويا",
        "response": "تويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكا",
        "response": "ميكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكايلا",
        "response": "ميكايلا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "راينر"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيترو",
        "response": "نيترو"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "لوسي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "سابو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينو",
        "response": "زينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيونا",
        "response": "فيونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديدارا",
        "response": "ديدارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكا",
        "response": "ميكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكايلا",
        "response": "ميكايلا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "راينر",
        "response": "راينر"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيترو",
        "response": "نيترو"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوسي",
        "response": "لوسي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابو",
        "response": "سابو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينو",
        "response": "زينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيونا",
        "response": "فيونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديدارا",
        "response": "ديدارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ستارك",
        "response": "ستارك"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
        {
        "question": "زيريف",
        "response": "زيريف"
    },
    {
        "question": "يونو",
        "response": "يونو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميريليونا",
        "response": "ميريليونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ران",
        "response": "ران"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماركو",
        "response": "ماركو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ويس",
        "response": "ويس"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيجيتا",
        "response": "فيجيتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فريزا",
        "response": "فريزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "كيوكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوثر",
        "response": "غوثر"
    },
    {
        "question": "سايتاما",
        "response": "سايتاما"
    },
    {
        "question": "جينوس",
        "response": "جينوس"
    },
    {
        "question": "غارو",
        "response": "غارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيلدريس",
        "response": "زيلدريس"
    },
    {
        "question": "شنايدر",
        "response": "شنايدر"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارشر",
        "response": "ارشر"
    },
    {
        "question": "غاتس",
        "response": "غاتس"
    },
    {
        "question": "غريفيث",
        "response": "غريفيث"
    },
    {
        "question": "شيسوي",
        "response": "شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايروين",
        "response": "ايروين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوك",
        "response": "هوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "بين بيكمان",
        "response": "بين بيكمان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلوا",
        "response": "كيلوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اني",
        "response": "اني"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانجي",
        "response": "هانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساشا",
        "response": "ساشا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايدو",
        "response": "كايدو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارتوريا",
        "response": "ارتوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باين",
        "response": "باين"
    },
    {
        "question": "موزان",
        "response": "موزان"
    },
    {
        "question": "دوفلامينغو",
        "response": "دوفلامينغو"
    },
    {
        "question": "لويد",
        "response": "لويد"
    },
    {
        "question": "انيا",
        "response": "انيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميليوداس",
        "response": "ميليوداس"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاكيميتشي",
        "response": "تاكيميتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوبيتو",
        "response": "اوبيتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيلامي",
        "response": "بيلامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ديانا",
        "response": "ديانا"
    },
    {
        "question": "بان",
        "response": "بان"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوكابي",
        "response": "اوكابي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تسونا",
        "response": "تسونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيتان",
        "response": "فيتان"
    },
    {
        "question": "يور",
        "response": "يور"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيرو",
        "response": "هيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "جوزو",
        "response": "جوزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يورويتشي",
        "response": "يورويتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاناكو",
        "response": "هاناكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "مايكي",
        "response": "مايكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "فايوليت",
        "response": "فايوليت"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوراك",
        "response": "كيوراك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ارمين",
        "response": "ارمين"
    },
    {
        "question": "البيرت",
        "response": "البيرت"
    },
    {
        "question": "توكا",
        "response": "توكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "باكوغا",
        "response": "باكوغا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "كيوكاي"
    }
]
